Jack Goldring Papers
© 2005 University of Connecticut
- Series II: Smith Act Trial, undated, 1954-1969
  - “The Communist Party and Secrecy, Concealment of Membership, Underground and Illegality”, undated (Box 1:, Folder 29)
  - Communist Party of Connecticut, undated (Box 1:, Folder 30)
  - Connecticut Volunteers for Civil Rights: printed materials, 1954-1955 (Box 1:, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 1:, Folder 32)
  - Court documents, undated (Box 1:, Folder 33)
  - Goldring, Jack: biographical information, 1954-1955 (Box 1:, Folder 34)
  - Memo on Racist Provisions of the Walter-McCarran Act, 1954 (Box 1:, Folder 35)
  - Newsclippings, 1954 (Box 1:, Folder 36)
  - Notes and reports, undated (Box 1:, Folder 37)
- Series III: Newspaper Clippings and Subject files, undated, 1944-1981
  - Amnesty Picnic, 1954 (Box 1:, Folder 37)
  - Anit-Communism articles, undated (Box 1:, Folder 38)
  - Discrimination in Housing, undated (Box 1:, Folder 39)
  - Speech by Honorable Thurston Morton, 1967 (Box 1:, Folder 40)
  - The Connecticut Unemployment Compensation Law, 1967 (Box 1:, Folder 41)
  - Welfare and Insurance Fund, 1968 (Box 1:, Folder 42)
  - Statewide Pension Fund, 1967 (Box 1:, Folder 43)
  - GM Publications, undated (Box 1:, Folder 44)
  - Labor History articles, undated (Box 1:, Folder 45-47)
  - Ribicoff, Abe, 1975-1976 (Box 1:, Folder 48)
  - Various articles, undated (Box 1:, Folder 49)
  - Film rolls, undated (Box 1:, Folder 50)
  - Clippings, undated (Box 2)
  - Clippings, 1944-1981 (Box 2)
  - Caricatures and political comics, undated (Box 2)
  - Labor history: articles, undated (Box 2)
  - Yearly union record graphs (Map-case OS)